<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Jean Monlong</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Jean Monlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2019 Jean Monlong</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a PhD candidate in genomics looking at copy number variation across healthy and disease genomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/home/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/publications/</guid>
      <description>Genotyping structural variants in pangenome graphs using the vg toolkit. bioRxiv 2019. G Hickey*, D Heller*,  J Monlong*, JA Sibbesen, J Siren, J Eizenga, E Dawson, E Garrison, A Novak, B Paten  Data/Code       Human copy number variants are enriched in regions of low mappability. Nucleic Acids Research 2018.  J Monlong, P Cossette, C Meloche, G Rouleau, SL Girard, G Bourque  Preprint Data/Code       Global characterization of copy number variants in epilepsy patients from whole genome sequencing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/home/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/talks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/home/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Between 2013 and 2018, I organized eight R workshops for the students of the Human Genetics department. Slides can be found here. For these workshops, I received a Certificate of Appreciation from the department.
Other teaching experiences include:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Notes</title>
      <link>/home/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/notes/</guid>
      <description>I regularly write down notes about the tools and programming languages I use in a separate website. There are instructions to setup my working environment (Emacs-based) or things I don&amp;rsquo;t use often enough to remember but enough to collectively waste my time re-googling. I also put some exploratory analyses that might be helpful or interesting to some.
HippocamPlus: my second memory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/home/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>